termdates.co.uk 2015-07-04

# Privacy Policy | Term Dates

We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website: [https://termdates.co.uk](https://termdates.co.uk/)

This Privacy Policy explains what we do with any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from any enquiry form that you complete whilst you visit our website.

**Information That We Collect**

We collect the following data from anyone that completes a newsletter sign up form on our website;

Name and Email Address

**Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you;

  * the latest news on term and holiday dates
  * other useful educational news
  * suggestions and discount vouchers for Days Out and things to do in the school holidays in your area.

**SSL Certificate**

The Term Dates website ([https://termdates.co.uk](https://termdates.co.uk/)) is a [TrustWave](https://ssl.trustwave.com/) Domain Validated SSL providing website visitors with the assurance that it is trustworthy and secure website

**Storing Your Personal Data**

We do our best to ensure that your data is stored securely. Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and occasionally such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

**Disclosing Your Information**

We will not disclose your details to any third party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy or where we are required by law.

**Access to Information**

You have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. We reserve the right to charge a fee of £20 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information.

**Contacting Us**

Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy by emailing us at [info@termdates.co.uk](mailto:info@termdates.co.uk)
